beauty queen of only eighteen she
仅仅18岁而美丽的小女王
had some trouble with herself
她自己内心有些烦恼
he was always there to help her
他总是会在守候着去帮助她
she always belonged to someone else
但她总是一直属于别人
i drove for miles and miles
我驾着车子 走了许多路程
and wound up at your door
终于来到你的家门前
i've had you so many times but somehow i want more
虽然我已经与你在一齐好几次  我想需要你的更多爱
i don't mind spending everyday
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
look for the girl with the broken smile
寻找着一个心碎微笑的女孩
ask her if she wants to stay awhile
询问她是否想与我停留片刻
and she will be loved *2
她会拥有我的爱
tap on my window, knock on my door
轻叩我的窗口 轻敲我的门
i want to make you feel beautiful
我只想令你觉得一切都美好
i know i tend to get so insecure
我知道我不太成熟
it doesn't matter anymore
那完全不要紧
it's not always rainbows and butterflies
世上不会总是有彩虹和蝴蝶
it's compromise that moves us along
这使到我们不断向前行
my heart is full and my door's always open
我的心和我的门总是为你打开
you can come anytime you want
只要你想的话 你就随时能来
i don't mind spending everyday
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
look for the girl with the broken smile
寻找着一个心碎微笑的女孩
ask her if she wants to stay awhile
询问她是否想与我停留片刻
and she will be loved *4
她会拥有我的爱
i know where you hide
我知道你在哪里
alone in your car
独自在你的车中
know all of the things
知道一切
that make you who you are
晓得令你变成如此的一切
i know that goodbye
我也知道再见
means nothing at all
并不意味什么
comes back and begs me to catch her every time she falls
在她每次失落时都能安慰她
yeah!tap on my window, knock on my door
轻叩我的窗口 轻敲我的门
i want to make you feel beautiful
我只想令你觉得一切都美好
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
look for the girl with the broken smile
寻找着一个心碎微笑的女孩
ask her if she wants to stay awhile
询问她是否想与我停留片刻
and she will be loved *4
她会拥有我的爱
我知道现场有很多人
大家来个大合唱
这首歌剩下的部分 你跟我一起唱吗？
我不会讲巴西语 但我尽量用英语解释
我要从这里对半分成
一.二，两个队
这边的观众！
and she will be loved *4
她会拥有我的爱
漂亮  你们太棒了！
等一下   这边的观众！
开始   大声点，大声点
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
这边的
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
and she will be loved she will...
告诉她我对她的心意
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
and she woll...i don't mind spending every day
她会...我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh
在倾盘大雨中 站在你家楼下的拐角处
i don't mind spending every day
我毫不介意花费我整天的时间
一 二 三  唱！
pleas don't try so hard to say goodbye
请别太快说再见
大家一起来
and she will be loved
她会拥有我的爱